followpics.net 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy

### INFORMATION COLLECTED:

Automatic Collection: Followpics.net uses common Internet technologies such as cookies and Web beacons to keep track of users’ interactions with the Site, Application and Services and to improve the quality of its service. Followpics.net may also collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address to track and aggregate non-personally identifiable information, your referring website addresses, browser type, domain name and access times.

  * Cookie: When you visit the Site, the Application and/or use a Service, Followpics.net’s servers send a cookie (a small file with a string of characters) to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you but would recognize your web browser; unless you choose to identify yourself to Followpics.net (through an account or otherwise), you will remain anonymous to Followpics.net. A cookie can be either session based (assigned to you each time you sign in) or persistent (it identifies browsers that have previously visited the Site, the Application or utilized the Services). Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies; however, if you do so, certain Site, Application or Service features may not work.
  * Web Beacon: A web beacon is an electronic image on a web page that recognizes certain types of information on your computer when you visit that particular web page.
  * IP Address: an Internet Protocol Address is a numerical label that is assigned to each computer on the Internet.
  * Referring website address: a referring website address identifies the address of the webpage you were on previously.
  * Browser: A browser is a software application used for retrieving, presenting, and traversing information resources on the World Wide Web.

In addition, Followpics.net may use third parties to track and analyze usage information, and in so doing may use third party cookies. Please see more detailed information below under “Third Parties” if you would like to know more about third party cookies.

Voluntary Collection: Followpics.net may collect certain information that personally identifies you (“PI”) or is protected personal information (“PPI”), such as your name, email address, website and login information for third party services (collectively referred to herein as “personally identifiable information”), if you choose to share such information. For example, this information may be requested as part of member registration, whereby we will create an account for your use of the Site and/or Application based on the PI you provide and you will become a member of Followpics.net. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide the requested information, you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in certain areas of the Site or the Application.

Publicly Posted: Information that you post on or through any public areas on the Site or the Application (or elsewhere on the Internet) may be collected and used by anyone and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others.

### HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

The information we collect enables Followpics.net to:

  * customize the advertising and content you see
  * fulfill your requests for Services
  * improve its services
  * contact and communicate with you
  * conduct research and analysis
  * provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients
  * provide you with additional information

### WHEN DO WE SHARE OR DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION?

We may share non-personal information with others, such as advertisers, sponsors and business partners, in aggregate anonymous form (meaning the information shared will not contain any personally identifiable information about you).

Other than as noticed in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, share, rent or otherwise disclose to third parties your personally identifiable information without your permission.

We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties who facilitate communication on behalf of Followpics.net for Followpics.net’s marketing and promotional efforts and/or for other information dissemination on behalf of Followpics.net.

We may sell, rent or share your personally identifiable information, provided we have received your prior permission, to third parties to send you marketing and promotional information not related to Followpics.net that may be of interest to you.

Your personally identifiable information may be transferred to third parties such as technical agents, payment processing vendors, consultants, advertising companies and among our affiliates for the performance of Followpics.net services or making products available to you.

All companies working for and with us that Followpics.net provides with your personally identifiable information are contractually required to protect your personally identifiable information and keep it confidential; they are not permitted to sell or otherwise disclose your information to third parties except as authorized by us and you or as permitted or required by law.

In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer, sell or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information if permitted by law or required to do so by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend our interests or the interests of our customers or users of our Site, Application or Services.

By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are authorizing us to share your personally identifiable information with and among Followpics.net affiliated companies.

### COOKIES & 3rd PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
